{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2583","name":"Priest Annex","address":"5901 Casper","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"044318","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.14360,42.33781","geojson":{"id":"2583","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.1435974249999,42.3378072450001]},"properties":{"name":"Priest Annex","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","address":"5901 Casper","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"044318","establishmentid":"2583","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/15/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"944","name":"Priest Elementary","address":"7840 Wagner St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3137","name":"La Rosita","address":"7831-49 McGraw St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5050","name":"El Rey De Las Arepas","address":"7701 McGraw St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5426","name":"Asty Time Inc.","address":"7340 McGraw Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","address":"5546 Chopin","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3481","name":"Matrix Head Start","address":"5690 Cecil","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"881","name":"Crazy Horse","address":"8140 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3579","name":"Brooksey's","address":"7625 W Warren Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3198","name":"Angel's Place","address":"7824 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2023","name":"La Sierra","address":"5400 Chopin","zipcode":"4821"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45994","inspectionDate":"2019-04-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44145","inspectionDate":"2018-11-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41992","inspectionDate":"2018-04-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40391","inspectionDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-301.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT for cooling and heating FOOD, and holding cold and hot FOOD, shall be sufficient in number and capacity to provide FOOD temperatures as required. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"cold holding","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide additional equipment to meet requirement above."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Eating","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Employee beverages","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Eat only in designated areas as restricted above."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) Dressing rooms shall be used by EMPLOYEES if the EMPLOYEES regularly change their clothes in the establishment.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be used for the orderly storage of EMPLOYEE clothing and other possessions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/designated storage area(s)","subItem":"for employee belongings storage","problemDescription":"Not used","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Employee belongings","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"A designated dressing room/area shall be provided and used."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Failed to notify the health department that an employee is diagnosed with a \"big 4\" illness","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"At the Allergens Training","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Notify as required by code."}]},{"inspectionid":"38646","inspectionDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36793","inspectionDate":"2016-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-05-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2583"}}